Ehren Holgersson

C# / Unity Developer



0415931243



ehrenholgersson@gmail.com



https://ehrenholgersson.github.io/ehrenholgersson



Artarmon NSW 2064

Profile

I am a passionate and creative Unity developer with several years of experience creating projects of my own. Last year I completed a certificate IV in Information Technology/Video Game Programming at NSW TAFE which allowed me to further develop myself to the point where I am now confident that I have the skills to enter the industry as a junior to mid-level developer. I have created projects within various genres, such as platformers, puzzles, and simulations, using C# and Unity tools. A sample of my projects can be seen on my web page, accessible from the above URL.

Prior to this I have enjoyed a long career as a Technical Support Engineer where I developed proven analytical problem solving, time management and customer relationship skills.

Skills

- Experienced working within Unity Environment
- Strong C# knowledge
- Demonstrated problem solving / analytical ability
- Good working knowledge of Git and GitHub
- Strong verbal and written communication abilities
- Familiar with Unreal Blueprint and C++ workflows
- Proven client and stakeholder relationship management skills

Education

Certificate IV in Information Technology (Video Game Programming)

Completed December 2023

Dell Certified Systems Engineer

Laptops, Desktops, Precision Workstations, and 13^{th} - 15^{th} Generation PowerEdge Servers

Higher School Certificate

Completed 2001

Employment History

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER 2 – SERVER Dell Australia // March 2020 – March 2023

Providing premium level technical support for a variety of enterprise-grade servers in rack, tower, or modular (blade) form factors, as well as relevant operating system hypervisor or management software.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER - WORKSTATION Dell Australia // July 2017 - March 2020

Premium level technical support for workstation grade systems such as the Dell Precision range. Assisting customers as well as on-site engineers with break-fix requests and general hardware or software troubleshooting.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER - CLIENT SYSTEMS Dell Australia // January 2011 - July 2017

Providing premium level technical support for Laptop and Desktop PCs. Assisting customers as well as on-site engineers with break-fix requests as well as general hardware or software troubleshooting.

TELEPHONE SUPPORT TECHNICAN

Gizmo // January 2009 - August 2009

Resolving a variety of technical issues for both Apple and Windows based computer systems via telephone and remote desktop.

SENIOR REP/ LEVEL 2 SUPPORT Engin // January 2008 - November 2008

Supervising customer service agents and troubleshooting faults not able to be resolved on first point of contact.